

28, Lorong Pandan Indah 1, Taman Pandan Indah, 13400 Butterworth, Penang, Malaysia.

Phone: +60124773683

Email address: teikhun0422@hotmail.com

PROFILE

A highly motivated and skilled data scientist with a strong background in computer science and statistical analysis. Proven experience in using a variety of data mining and machine learning techniques to solve complex problems. Proficient in Python, R, and SQL.

EXPERIENCE

Australian National University, COMP6240 Relational Databases **Tutor**

Australian National University / June 2022 - Dec 2022

- Teach courses on database management and design, including the use of SQL to define, query, and manipulate a relational database.
- Introduce database design methods based on functional dependencies and normal forms for evaluating the quality of a database design.
- Cover topics such as query processing and optimization, transaction management, and security management in a relational database management system.

Internship as Data Scientist, Petroliam Nasional Berhad

Group Digital, KL / November 2020 - July 2021

- Used regular expression and other text pre-processing features in python to automate the extraction of information from corporate business database, minimizing data quality issues by 90%.
- Utilized Object Oriented Programming (class and subclass) for the conversion of data from JSON to panda, performed queries such as append, split and find all to categorize the database.
- Applied techniques like natural processing language processing and text mining on corporate business database (Fuzzy mapping), increased mapping accuracy by 80%.
- Performed feature selection using filter, wrapper and embedded method to identify the significant predictors for machine learning model, compared the results with key influencer analysis from Power BI.
- Forecasted the profitability of oil and gas investment by generating linear regression model based on the significant predictors, provided data visualization using matplotlib, seaborn and Power Bl.
- Assisted in unsupervised clustering model training using K mean and hierarchical algorithms for oil and gas offshore platform resource development.

EDUCATION

Master of Applied Data Analytics, Australian National University, Canberra, Australia

July 2021 - Dec 2022

- Major in Neural Network and Document Analysis
- CGPA 6.42/7 cumulative.
- Weight Averaged Mark, 80/100.
- Relevant courseworks: Information Retrieval, Data Mining, Relational Database, Deep Learning and etc.

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ teik-hun-ang-60233a1b9/

SKILLS

Analytical Thinking Skills

Adaptability

Time Management

Leadership

Power Bl

Python

Neural Network

Machine Learning (SKlearn)

Database SQL

Data Wrangling

Optimization

MEMBERSHIP

Board of Engineer Malaysia, **Graduate Engineer**

Institution of Civil Engineers, ICE

CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

Nov 2020

Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Engineer Associate Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES AND AWARDS

ANU+ Award

July 2021 - Dec 2022

 The ANU+ Award is a program that formally recognizes experience and contribution achieved through volunteering. Volunteer 40 hours in computing related field.

CLUBS & SPORT

- Head of Ceremony and Protocol department, Medical Camp, Rotaract Club.
- Assistance Head of Club Serve Department, Rotaract Club.

ADVANCED COURSES

Data & Al Essentials, IBM

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/6a6700f0-a3ef-4b0a-8fc23475c0897dd6?source=linked_in_profile

Machine Learning A-Z™: Hands-On Python & R In Data Science, Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-2fee7097-3f3f-430a-ab8a-3196e8f5be89/

70-778, DA-100: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Power BI, Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-7b5b1dd2-3225-46bc-a731-58adb9faa07c/

Master statistics & machine learning: intuition, math, code, Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-cbe8daad-70a6-4c83-bac8-eba86c90ae84/

Data Science Math Skills, Coursera

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/AFA7VK58ZXVK

Computer Vision Basic, Coursera

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/GN2ZGC9GMTNJ

Relevant coursework:

Descriptive and inferential statistics, T-tests, correlation, ANOVA, Linear Regression, Classification, Clustering, Reinforcement Learning, Natural Language Processing, Deep Learning, Dimensionality Reduction, Model Selection and Boosting.

HOBBIES

Gym and Cooking

LANGUAGES

Chinese

English

Malay

French

PUBLICATION

Insight on Extraction and Characterization of Biopolymers as the Green Coagulants for Microalgae Harvesting

Q2, MDPI Water, May 2020 https://www.mdpi.com/2073-4441/12/5/1388

Encyclopedia, Sept 2020 https://encyclopedia.pub/1462

REFERENCES

A/Prof Qing Wang

School of Computing

The Australian National University Canberra, ACT 0200

+61(0)261254625

ging.wang@anu.edu.au

Dr Vikram Sorathia

Head (Data Science) at PETRONAS

+(60)18-9826762

vikrambhai.sorathia@petronas .com



A/Prof. Qing Wang School of Computing The Australian National University Canberra, ACT 0200 Australia

Phone: +61 (0)2 6125 4625 Email: qing.wang@anu.edu.au

Date: December 1, 2022

Recommendation Letter for Teik Hun Ang

It is my great pleasure to write this letter of recommendation for Mr. Teik Hun Ang. I am presently an Associate Professor at the School of Computing at the Australian National University (ANU), Canberra, Australia. My research is focused on data management, analysis, and algorithms, particularly on graph-structured data.

I have known Teik Hun Ang since September 2021, when he was an undergraduate student in an introductory database course (COMP2400 Relational Databases) and I was the course lecturer. In this course, he very quickly achieved a solid understanding of both the bigger picture of the theoretical foundation and the specific practical skills he would need to accomplish. Teik Hun Ang was one of the top students in this course and he received an outstanding mark 92 out of 100.

In 2022, we were fortunate to have Teik Hun Ang as a tutor to help with this course. In particular, Teik Hun Ang helped to interact with students and deliver labs/tutorials. Teik Hun Ang's tutorials were very well prepared and delivered. He was easily approachable to our students and was eager to help them learn better. His tutoring effort was recognized by unanimous satisfactory feedback from students in his tutorials. Teik Hun Ang is an excellent team player, both as a leader (e.g., leading labs/tutorials) and partner (e.g., in collaborative tasks such marking). He has worked effectively with the course convenor, other tutors and me in this course. We truly enjoyed working with Teik Hun Ang.

In summary, I strongly recommend Teik Hun Ang for your organisation. Do not hesitate to contact me if you should need any additional information.

Best regards,

Qing Wang